A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of XXX, 1991.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Constituent Correspondence of XXX,
1991.
The Library of Virginia
34589
Virginia. Governor (1990-1994: XXX).
XX cu. ft. (XX boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by series.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 34588 was transferred by XXX, XX.
Historical Information
XX
XX
Scope and Content
XX
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1991
Series II. Governor's Office, 1991
Contents List
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1991.
  - Secretary of Administration: Compensation Board, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: Early Retirement, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment Services, Office of, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: Grievances, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: Human Rights, Council on, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Administration: Local Government, Commission on, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Furloughs (1 of 3), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Furloughs (2 of 3), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Furloughs (3 of 3), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Health insurance benefits, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Pensions, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Salaries, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Administration: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Administration: State Board of Elections, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Administration: State budget cuts, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: State employee benefits, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Governmental Employee Association, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Pension, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (1 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (2 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (3 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (4 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (5 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (6 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development (7 of 7), 1991. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of - Disaster area (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of - Disaster area (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Center for Innovative Technology, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commerce, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commerce, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Consumer Affairs, Division of, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Cosmetology, Virginia Board for, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Farmers' Market, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Films, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Forestry, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (1 of 5), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (2 of 5), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (3 of 5), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (4 of 5), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (5 of 5), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Development Authority, Virginia, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Partnership Fund, Virginia (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Partnership Fund, Virginia (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Milk Commission, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: NASA, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Open supply, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Pesticide Control Board, Virginia, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Real estate, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Relocating to Virginia, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Rural development, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: State budget cuts, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Tobacco Row (Richmond), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Tourism, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Commission for the Arts, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (1 of 4), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (2 of 4), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (3 of 4), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (4 of 4), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Port Authority, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Racing Commission, 1991. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Welcome Centers, 1991. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World trade (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World trade (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education (1 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education (2 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education (3 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education (4 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education (5 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education (6 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education (7 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education (8 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education (9 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education (10 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education (11 of 11), 1991. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Center for Innovative Technology, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: Child day care services, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: Christopher Newport College, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: College of William and Mary, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: Dropout prevention, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Drug abuse prevention, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Drug testing, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Educational Opportunity for All Virginians, Commission on, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: English Language Movement (mass mailing) (1 of 3), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: English Language Movement (mass mailing) (2 of 3), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: English Language Movement (mass mailing) (3 of 3), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: Frontier Culture Museum, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: George Mason University, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: Governor's School Program, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Gunston Hall, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: James Madison Univerity, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: Jobs for Virginia graduates, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: Longwood College, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: Mary Washington College, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Education: Northern Virginia Community College, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Education: Old Dominion University, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Education: Radford University, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Education: School boards (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Education: School boards (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Education: School funding, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Education: Science Museum of Virginia, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts (1 of 3), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts (2 of 3), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts (3 of 3), 1991. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: State Education Assistance Authority, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: Teachers' salaries, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Bridgeport - Commencement address, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Community College System, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Military Institute, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State Library and Archives, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State University, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Vocational Industrial Clubs of America, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Finance: Accounts, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Finance: Cigarette tax, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Finance: Comptroller, Dept. of the, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Finance: Economic Advisory Council, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Finance: Escheats, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Finance: Food tax, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Finance: Gasoline tax, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Finance: General, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Finance: Lottery proceeds, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Finance: Personal property tax, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Finance: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Finance: Prescription drug tax, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Finance: Real estate tax, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Finance: Retirement income taxation, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Finance: Sales tax, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Finance: State budget (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Finance: State budget (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Finance: Tax amnesty, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (1 of 4), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (2 of 4), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (3 of 4), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (4 of 4), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Finance: Treasury, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (1 of 6), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (2 of 6), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (3 of 6), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (4 of 6), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (5 of 6), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (6 of 6), 1991. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Abortion, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adolescent pregnancy, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adoption, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aging, Dept. for the, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aid to Dependent Children, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Central Virginia Training Center, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Certificate of Public Need, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child abuse, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child custody (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child custody (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Day Care and Early Childhood, Council on, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (1 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (2 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (3 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (4 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (5 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (6 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Support Enforcement, Division of (7 of 7), 1991. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Children, Dept. for, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. for the, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Eastern State Hospital, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Emergency Medical Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Family Support Act, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Family Violence Prevention, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Geriatric Treatment Center, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Governor's Employment and Training Dept., 1991. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care for All Virginians, Commission on, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of (1 of 3), 1991. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of (2 of 3), 1991. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of (3 of 3), 1991. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Services Cost Review Council, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: HIV/AIDS, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Indians, Council on, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Infant mortality, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Insurance, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Job Training Partnership Act, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medicare and Medicaid, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, Dept. of (1 of 3), 1991. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, Dept. of (2 of 3), 1991. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, Dept. of (3 of 3), 1991. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Shenandoah Geriatric Treatment Center, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Security, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (1 of 5) 1991. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (2 of 5), 1991. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (3 of 5), 1991. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (4 of 5), 1991. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (5 of 5), 1991. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: State Budget Cuts, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Status of Women, Council on the, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Visually Handicapped, Dept. for the, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Vital Records, Division of, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Volunteerism, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Weatherization Program, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Western State Hospital, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Yourh and Families, Council on, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Bottle Bill, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Buena Vista Power Plant and Flood Control, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Chesapeake Bay Preservation (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Chesapeake Bay Preservation (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Clean Air Act, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environment, Council on the (1 of 3), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environment, Council on the (2 of 3), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Environment, Council on the (3 of 3), 1991. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Historic Resources, Dept., 1991. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Landfills, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Marine Resources Commission, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Medical Waste Incinerators, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Recycling, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: State budget cuts, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: State Water Control Board, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Swan hunting, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Virginia Boating Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Virginia Museum of Natural History, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Waste Management, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Wildlife, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Yard waste composting, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Correctional Education, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (1 of 6), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (2 of 6), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (3 of 6), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (4 of 6), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (5 of 6), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Public Safety: Corrections, Dept. of (6 of 6), 1991. (Box 14, Folder 10)